DIEGO CARRASCO



BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

Guayaquil, Ecuador

+593 967 805 820

diego.carrasco13@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

Christian by conviction and not by religion, I am 31 years old, I am Ecuadorian and I work with the purpose of creating strategic solutions to substantial problems of companies from an interdisciplinary perspective, to achieve continuous improvement.

My academic background was based on German model of the **Duale**

Hochschule Baden Württemberg

focused on Production and Logistics /Costs and Finance and general knowledge in Human Talent (HR) / Marketing and Sales.

EDUCATION

Instituto 11

| 2019-2020

Course

Disruptive Entrepreneurship Monterrey, Mexico (Virtual)

Universitat de Barcelona | 2016-2018

Master Degree

Business Research

Barcelona, Spain

Universitat Pompeu Fabra | 2015-2016

Master Degree

Entrepreneurship and Innovation

Mataro, Spain

Universidad Católica

I 2009-2013

Bachelor Degree Business Administration Guayaquil, Ecuador

REFERENCES

Giovanni Giusti, Ph.D Director of the graduate program in Entrepreneurship and Innovation of Tecnocampus - UPF

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 (ACTUAL)

TM Restaurant

Guavaguil, Ecuador

Business Development Manager

Business Model / Dirección de Operaciones / Familiar Business

BOHLE S.A.U., 2020 - 2021

Barcelona, Spain

Business Consultant

Networking / Mercadotecnia / Política Comercial

2019 - 2020 LIGHTHOUSE,

Zaragoza | Vilafranca, Spain

Business Assessor

Digital Marketing / Branding / Sales Department

2018 - 2019 (**TECUM Management.** Cerdanyola, Spain

Assistant Sales Manager

Sales Prospecting / Sales Follow-up

TECNOCAMPUS Incubadora, Mataro, Spain

PROJECT DELYRA: Co-Founder

PROJECT STM Restaurant: Business Consultant

MUEI Summer Entrepreneurship: Associate Professor

CORE COMPETENCIES



2017 - 2018









Communication Business **Skills**

Development

Customer Service

Staff Management Research Skills

LENGUAGES

Español Inglés Catalán



SKILLS

Teamwork Emotional Intelligence Decision Making

INTERESTS







